Guide to the Montana State University Extension Service Records 1912-1970
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- County and Home Demonstration Agents Annual Reports, 1916-1970; 1
  - Stillwater County; Darrell Fenner, Alice Hancock, JoAnne Fulbright, Mary K. Simmons, 1959 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Stillwater County; Darrell E. Fenner, Mary Kay Simmons, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Stillwater County; Darrell E. Fenner, Mary K. Simmons, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Stillwater County; Darrell E. Fenner, Mary Kay Simmons, Shirley Kay Wheeler, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Stillwater County; Darrell E. Fenner, Kay Schauer, 1963 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Stillwater County; Darrell Fenner, Kay Schauer, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Stillwater County; Darrell Fenner, Shirley Kay Schauer, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Stillwater County; Darrell Fenner, Lois Lohr, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Stillwater County, 1967-1970 (Box 59, Folder 15-18)
  - Sweetgrass County; D. S. Fox, 1917 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Sweetgrass County; Orpha Brown, H.D.A., 1930-1932 (Box 59, Folder 20-22)
  - Sweetgrass County; E. R. Cook, Emergency Agent, 1934 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Sweetgrass County; E. R. Cook, C.A., 1935 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Sweetgrass County; Martha Haynes, H.D.A., 1935 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Sweetgrass County; E. R. Cook, 1936-1941 (Box 59, Folder 26-31)
  - Sweetgrass County; E. R. Cook, H. M. Oefstos, 1942 (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Sweetgrass County; H. M. Oefstos, C.A., 1943-1947 (Box 59, Folder 33-37)
  - Sweetgrass County; F. B. Peterson, 1948-1955 (Box 59, Folder 38-45)
  - Sweetgrass County; F. B. Peterson, Louise Guild, 1956-1957 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
  - Sweetgrass County; F. B. Peterson, Agent; Louise Guild, H.D.A., 1958-1959 (Box 60, Folder 3-4)
  - Sweetgrass County; F. B. Peterson, Louise Guild, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 5-6)
  - Sweetgrass County; F. B. Peterson, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Sweetgrass County; F. B. Peterson, Robert G. Racicot, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Sweetgrass County; Robert G. Racicot, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Sweetgrass County; Ellis Williams, 1965-1966 (Box 60, Folder 10-11)
  - Sweetgrass County, 1967-1970 (Box 60, Folder 12-15)
  - Teton County; John M. Davis, 1915-1916 (Box 60, Folder 16-17)
  - Teton County; W. S. Murdock, 1917 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Teton County; W. S. Murdock, A. J. Ogaard, Robert Clarkson, 1918 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Teton County; Robert Clarkson, 1919-1924 (Box 60, Folder 20-25)
  - Teton County; Robert Clarkson, C.A., 1925-1933 (Box 60, Folder 26-34)
  - Teton County; Robert Clarkson, F. S. Willson, 1934 (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Teton County; F. S. Willson, C.A., 1935 (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - Teton County; Fred S. Willson, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - Teton County; Fred S. Willson, 1937 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Teton County; F. S. Willson, 1938 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Teton County; Lois Knowlton, H.D.A., 1938 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Teton County; F. S. Willson, 1939 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Teton County; Lois Knowlton, H.D.A., 1939 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Teton County; S. N. Halvorson, C.A., 1940 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Teton County; Lois K. Stephens, H.D.A., 1940 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Teton County; Lois K. Stephens, Margaret Conlon, H.D.A.s, 1940 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Teton County; Stanley N. Halvorson, C.A., 1941 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Teton County; Margaret Conlon, H.D.A., 1941 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Teton County; S. N. Halvorson, 1942 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Teton County; Margaret Conlon, H.D.A., 1942 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Teton County; S. N. Halvorson, C.A., 1943 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Teton County; Margaret B. Conlon, H.D.A., 1943 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Teton County; Glenn Baird, C.A., 1944 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Teton County; Frieda Schroder, H.D.A., 1944 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Teton County; M. H. Zimmerman, C.A., 1945 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Teton County; Frieda Schroder, H.D.A., 1945 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Teton County; Raymond Kelly, C.A., 1946 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Teton County; Frieda Schroder, H.D.A., 1946 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Teton County; Raymond Kelly, C.A., 1947 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Teton County; Frieda Schroder, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Teton County; Ray Kelly, 1948 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Teton County; Frieda Schroder, H.D.A., 1948 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Teton County; Ray Kelly, Stanley Howard, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Teton County; Frieda Schroder, H.D.A., 1949 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Teton County; Ray Kelly, Howard Connell, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Teton County; Frieda Schroder, H.D.A., 1950 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Teton County; Ray Kelly, Frieda Schroder, Howard Connell, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Teton County; Raymond Kelly, Frieda R. Schroder, Howard Connell, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Teton County; Raymond Kelly, Frieda Schroder, Parker E. Heikes, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Teton County; Raymond Kelly, Parker E. Heikes, Frieda R. Schroder, 1954 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Teton County; Raymond Kelly, Frieda Schroder, Eugene Heikes, Williams J. Collins, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Teton County; Frieda R. Schroder, Raymond Kelly, Wm. Collins, M. J. Jackson, Gladys Scott, 1956 (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Teton County; Raymond Kelly William Collins, Frieda Schroder, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Teton County; Ray Kelly, Agent; Frieda Schroder, H.D.A.; Bill Collins, Assoc. Agent, Ross Peace, Assoc. Agent, 1958 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Teton County; Raymond Kelly, Agent; Frieda Schroder, H.D.A.; Ross Peace, Assoc. Agent, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Teton County; Raymond Kelly, Frieda Schroder, Ross Peace, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Teton County; Raymond Kelly, Ross D. Peace, Frieda R. Schroder, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Teton County; Raymond Kelly, Frieda Schroder, Ross Peace, LeRoy Luft, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Teton County; Raymond Kelly, LeRoy Luft, Frieda Schroder, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Teton County; Raymond Kelly Frieda Schroder, Robert Reiquam, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Teton County; Frieda Schroder, Raymond Kelly, George Goodwin, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Teton County; Raymond Kelly, Frieda Schroder, Mike Goodwin, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Teton County, 1967-1970 (Box 62, Folder 11-14)
  - Toole County; F. J. Chase, F. E. Ostrander, 1917 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Toole County; C. A. Michels, 1918-1920 (Box 62, Folder 16-18)
  - Toole County; M. H. Ostrem, 1930-1933 (Box 62, Folder 19-22)
  - Toole County; Pat McElliott, 1934 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Toole County; P. D. McElliott, 1935-1938 (Box 62, Folder 24-27)
  - Toole County; Pat McElliott, 1939 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Toole County; P. D. McElliott, C.A., 1940 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Toole County; Pat D. McElliott, 1941 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Toole County; P. D. McElliott, 1942 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Toole County; Pat McElliott, C.A., 1943 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Toole County; Pat McElliott, C.A., 1944 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Toole County; Pat McElliott, A. W. Elting, C.A.s, 1945 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Toole County; Robert F. Bucher, C.A., 1946 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Toole County; R. F. Bucher, C.A., 1947 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Toole County; Louise S. Shunk, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Toole County; R. F. Bucher, 1948 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Toole County; Mrs. Louise S. Shunk, H.D.A., 1948 (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - Toole County; R. F. Bucher, 1949-1950 (Box 62, Folder 40-41)
  - Toole County; R. F. Bucher, 1951-1953 (Box 63, Folder 1-3)
  - Toole County; Robert F. Bucher, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Toole County; Robert Bucher, Clemens Brigl, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Toole County; Clemens Brigl, 1956-1960 (Box 63, Folder 6-10)
  - Toole County; Clemens Brigl, Malcolm E. Adams, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Toole County; Malcolm E. Adams, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Toole County; Malcolm Adams, Anton Sundsted, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Toole County; Anton Sundsted, 1964-1966 (Box 63, Folder 14-16)
  - Toole County, 1967-1970 (Box 63, Folder 17-20)
  - Treasure County; J. K. Mueller, Emergency Agent, 1944 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Valley County; Ray E. Cannon, 1917 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Valley County; Murray E. Stebbins, 1918-1919 (Box 63, Folder 23-24)
  - Valley County; Gertrude Erickson, H.D.A., 1919 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Valley County; Murray E. Stebbins, 1920 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Valley County; Gertrude Erickson, H.D.A., 1920 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Valley County; Murray E. Stebbins, 1921 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Valley County; Murray E. Stebbins, 1922 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Valley County; Gertrude Erickson, H.D.A., 1922 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Valley County; Murray E. Stebbins, 1923 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Valley County; Gertrude Erickson, H.D.A., 1923 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Valley County; Murray E. Stebbins, 1924 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Valley County; Gertrude Erickson, H.D.A., 1924 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Valley County; Murray E. Stebbins, 1925 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Valley County; Gertrude Erickson, H.D.A., 1925 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Valley County; C. H. Willson, C.A., 1926 (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Valley County; Gertrude Erickson, H.D.A., 1926 (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Valley County; C. H. Willson, C.A., 1927 (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Valley County; Gertrude Erickson, H.D.A., 1927 (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Valley County; C. H. Willson, C.A., 1928 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Valley County; Ida Hagman, H.D.A., 1928 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Valley County; C. H. Willson, C.A., 1929 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Valley County; Florence Elliott, H.D.A., 1929 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Valley County; C. H. Willson, C.A., 1930 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Valley County; Florence Elliott, H.D.A., 1930 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Valley County; C. H. Willson, C.A., 1931 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Valley County; Florence P. Elliott, H.D.A., 1931 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Valley County; Newspaper Clippings Concerning Extension Work, 1931 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Valley County; C. H. Willson, C.A., 1932 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Valley County; Florence Elliott, H.D.A., 1932 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Valley County; C. H. Willson, C.A., 1933 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Valley County; Florence Elliott, H.D.A., 1933 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Valley County; C. H. Willson, Mrs. Florence Elliott, 1934 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Valley County; Mrs. Florence Elliott, H.D.A., 1934 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Valley County; C. J. Spalding, C.A., 1935 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Valley County; Florence Elliott, H.D.A., 1935 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Valley County; Chas. E. Jarrett, 1936 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Valley County; Mrs. Florence Elliott, H.D.A., 1936 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Valley County; Charles E. Jarrett, 1937 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Valley County; Mrs. Florence Elliott, H.D.A., 1937 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Valley County; Chas. E. Jarrett, 1938 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Valley County; Mrs. Florence P. Elliott, H.D.A., 1938 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Valley County; Chas. E. Jarrett, 1939 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Valley County; Florence P. Elliott, H.D.A., 1939 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Valley County; Chas. E. Jarrett, C.A., 1940 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Valley County; Florence Elliott, H.D.A., 1940 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Valley County; Chas. E. Jarrett, 1941 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Valley County; Mrs. Florence Elliott, H.D.A., 1941 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Valley County; C. E. Jarrett, J. K. McGibney, 1942 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Valley County; Mrs. Florence P. Elliott, H.D.A., 1942 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Valley County; James K. McGibney, C.A., 1943 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Valley County; Florence P. Elliott, H.D.A., 1943 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Valley County; Jas. K. McGibney, C.A., 1944 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Valley County; Iva Holladay, H.D.A., 1944 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Valley County; Jas. K. McGibney, C.A., 1945 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Valley County; Iva Holladay, H.D.A., 1945 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Valley County; Robert M. Rovig, C.A., 1946 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Valley County; Iva Holladay, H.D.A., 1946 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Valley County; W. R. Aldworth, C.A., 1947 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Valley County; Iva L. Holladay, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Valley County; W. R. Aldworth, 1948 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Valley County; Iva L. Holladay, H.D.A., 1948 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Valley County; W. R. Aldworth, 1949 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Valley County; Iva L. Holladay, H.D.A., 1949 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Valley County; Dana Schrupp, 1950 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Valley County; Iva L. Holladay, H.D.A., 1950 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Valley County; Dana O. Schrupp, Iva L. Holladay, 1951 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Valley County; Dana O. Schrupp, Iva L. Holladay, 1952 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Valley County; Dana Schrupp, Iva Holladay, 1953 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Valley County; Dana O. Schrupp, Leo F. Kleffner, Iva L. Holladay, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Valley County; Iva L. Holladay, Maud R. Sharer, Marie Roeseler, Dana Schrupp, Leo Kleffner, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Valley County; Dana O. Schrupp, Iva L. Holladay, Maud Sharer, Alfred Thorson, Leo Kleffner, Marie Roeseler, 1956 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Valley County; Dana O. Schrupp, Iva L. Holladay, Alfred G. Thorson, Maud R. Sharer, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Valley County; I. L. Holladay, H.D.A.; M. R. Sharer, Assoc. H.D.A.; D. O. Schrupp, Agent; A. G. Thorson, Assoc. Agent, 1958 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Valley County; Dana Schrupp, Agent; Iva Holladay, H.D.A.; Alfred Thorson, Assoc. Agent; Maud Sharer, Assoc. H.D.A., 1959 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Valley County; Dana Schrupp, Iva Holladay, Alfred Thorson, Maud Sharer, Amarlys Weinmeister, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Valley County; Dana Schrupp, Alfred Thorson, B. M. Nagle, Iva Holladay, Amarlys Weinmeister, Quanbeck, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Valley County; Alfred G. Thorson, Iva Holladay, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Valley County; Alfred Thorson, Iva Holladay, 1963-1964 (Box 65, Folder 31-32)
  - Valley County; Alfred Thorson, Sharon Fiegle, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Valley County; Alfred Thorson, Sharon Orednick, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Valley County, 1967-1970 (Box 66, Folder 3-6)
  - Wheatland County; A. D. Anderson, 1920 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Wheatland County; A. D. Anderson, 1921 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Wheatland County; A. D. Anderson, 1922 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Wheatland County; K. P. Jones, 1934 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Wheatland County; K. P. Jones, C.A., 1935 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Wheatland County; K. P. Jones, 1936-1939 (Box 66, Folder 12-15)
  - Wheatland County; K. P. Jones, C.A., 1940 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Wheatland County; Kenneth P. Jones, 1941 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Wheatland County; K. P. Jones, 1942 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Wheatland County; K. P. Jones, C.A., 1943-1946 (Box 66, Folder 19-22)
  - Wibaux County; Walter E. Botsford, 1917 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Wibaux County; M. P. Ostby, C.A., 1928-1943 (Box 66, Folder 24-36)
  - Wibaux County; M. P. Ostby, B. L. Dooley, Chas. Bordsen, W. N. Alexander, C.A.s, 1944 (Box 66, Folder 40)
  - Wibaux County; Ross D. Peace, 1949 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Wibaux County; Ross Peace, 1950 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Wibaux County; Ross D. Peace, 1951 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Wibaux County; Wayne W. Parris, 1951 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Wibaux County; Melvin Nielson, 1952 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Wibaux County; Melvin E. Nielson, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Wibaux County; Michael Rykunyk, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Wibaux County; Melvin Nielson, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Wibaux County; Melvin E. Nielson, 1956-1957 (Box 67, Folder 9-10)
  - Wibaux County; Lee Rovig, C.A., 1958 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Wibaux County; Lee R. Rovig, C.A., 1959 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Wibaux County; Lee Rovig, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Wibaux County; Leslie W. Sonder, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Wibaux County; Jess A. Kovanda, 1962-1966 (Box 67, Folder 15-19)
  - Wibaux County, 1967-1970 (Box 67, Folder 20-23)
  - Yellowstone County; Fred Bennion, 1917 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Yellowstone County; H. S. Brossard, 1918-1920 (Box 67, Folder 25-27)
  - Yellowstone County; Inez Foster, H.D.A., 1920 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Yellowstone County; H. S. Brossard, 1921 (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - Yellowstone County; Inez Foster Bell, H.D.A., 1921 (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - Yellowstone County; H. S. Brossard, 1922 (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - Yellowstone County; Inez Foster Bell, H.D.A., 1922 (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - Yellowstone County; H. S. Brossard, W. P. Stapleton, 1923 (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - Yellowstone County; Inez Foster Bell, H.D.A., 1923 (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - Yellowstone County; W. P. Stapleton, Chas. Ruzicka, 1924 (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - Yellowstone County; Edith Sloan, H.D.A., 1924 (Box 67, Folder 36)
  - Yellowstone County; Inez Foster Bell, H.D.A., 1924 (Box 67, Folder 37)
  - Yellowstone County; C. H. Ruzicka, C.A., 1925 (Box 67, Folder 38)
  - Yellowstone County; Edith Sloan, H.D.A., 1925 (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - Yellowstone County; C. H. Ruzicka, C.A., 1926 (Box 67, Folder 40)
  - Yellowstone County; Edith Sloan, H.D.A., 1926 (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - Yellowstone County; C. H. Ruzicka, C.A., 1927 (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - Yellowstone County; Edith A. Sloan, H.D.A., 1927 (Box 67, Folder 43)
  - Yellowstone County; R. B. McKee, C.A., 1928 (Box 67, Folder 44)
  - Yellowstone County; Edith Sloan, Doris Anderson, H.D.A.s, 1928 (Box 67, Folder 45)
  - Yellowstone County; R. B. McKee, C.A., 1929 (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Yellowstone County; Doris Anderson, H.D.A., 1929 (Box 67, Folder 47)
  - Yellowstone County; R. B. McKee, C.A., 1930 (Box 67, Folder 48)
  - Yellowstone County; Doris Anderson, H.D.A., 1930 (Box 67, Folder 49)
  - Yellowstone County; R. B. McKee, C.A., 1931 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Yellowstone County; Doris I. Anderson, H.D.A., 1931 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Yellowstone County; R. B. McKee, C.A., 1932 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Yellowstone County; Doris Anderson, H.D.A., 1932 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Yellowstone County; R. B. McKee, C.A., 1933 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Yellowstone County; Doris Anderson, H.D.A., 1933 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Yellowstone County; R. B. McKee, Mrs. Doris I. Anderson, 1934 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Yellowstone County; Doris Anderson, H.D.A., 1934 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Yellowstone County; R. B. McKee, C.A., 1935 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Yellowstone County; Doris I. Anderson, H.D.A., 1935 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Yellowstone County; R. B. McKee, 1936 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Yellowstone County; Mrs. Doris Anderson, H.D.A., 1936 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Yellowstone County; Keith Sime, C.A., 1937 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Yellowstone County; Mrs. Doris I. Anderson, H.D.A., Miss Margaret Conlon, Acting H.D.A., 1937 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Yellowstone County; Keith Sime, 1938 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Yellowstone County; Mrs. Doris I. Anderson, Miss Margaret Conlon, H.D.A.s, 1938 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Yellowstone County; Keith Sime, 1939 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Yellowstone County; Doris Anderson, Margaret Conlon, H.D.A.s, 1939 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Yellowstone County; Keith Sime, C.A., 1940 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Yellowstone County; Doris I. Anderson, H.D.A., 1940 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Yellowstone County; Keith Sime, William H. Jones, C.A.s; Lambert Hruska, Acting Agent, 1941 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Yellowstone County; Mrs. Doris I. Anderson, H.D.A.; Pages 1-102, 1941 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Yellowstone County; Mrs. Doris I. Anderson, H.D.A.; Pages 103-184, 1941 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Yellowstone County; Wm. H. Jones, 1942 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Yellowstone County; Doris Anderson, H.D.A., 1942 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Yellowstone County; W. H. Jones, Owen S. Wirak, B. L. Dooley, C.A.s; Pages 1-94, 1943 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Yellowstone County; W. H. Jones, Owen S. Wirak, B. L. Dooley, C.A.s; Pages 95-234, 1943 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - Yellowstone County; Doris I. Anderson, Margaret B. Conlon, H.D.A.s, 1943 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Yellowstone County; W. H. Jones, C.A.; B. L. Dooley, Assistant Agent, 1944 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Yellowstone County; Margaret Conlon, Lillian Stone, H.D.A.s, 1944 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Yellowstone County; W. H. Jones, C.A.; L. E. Flesch, Assistant Agent, 1945 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Yellowstone County; Lillian Stone, H.D.A.; Lutie Weedman, Lois Hodgskiss, Assistant H.D.A.'s, 1945 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Yellowstone County; W. H. Jones, C.A., 1946 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Yellowstone County; Lillian Stone, Lutie Weedman, H.D.A.'s, 1946 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Yellowstone County; W. H. Jones, 1947 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Yellowstone County; Billings Alfreda R. Forswall, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Yellowstone County; Theodore H. Alexander, 1948 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Yellowstone County; Alfreda Forswall, H.D.A.; Ruth Otten, Assistant Agent, 1948 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Yellowstone County; Ted Alexander, Owen Wirak, 1949 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Yellowstone County; Alfreda R. Forswall, Carol Gibbons, H.D.A.s, 1949 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Yellowstone County; Theodor H. Alexander, 1950 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Yellowstone County; Alfreda Forswall, Carol Gibbons, H.D.A.s, 1950 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Yellowstone County; T. H. Alexander, Alfreda Forswall, Owen Wirak, Averill Perkins, 1951 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Yellowstone County; Theo. Alexander, Alfreda R. Forswall, Allison Golden, Averill Perkins, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Yellowstone County; Eugene E. Coombs, Alfreda Forswall, Howard Tegland, Stella Kittams, 1953 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Yellowstone County; Donald J. Luebbe, Arne Skedsvold, Alfreda Forswall, Stella Kittams, 1954 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Yellowstone County; Don Luebbe, Alfreda Forswall, Arne Skedsvold, Stella Kittams, Ruth K. Pierson, 1955 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Yellowstone County; Donald Luebbe, Alfreda Forswall, Charlene Niebel, Arne Skedsvold, Ruth Pierson, 1956 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Yellowstone County; Luebbe, Forswall, Skedsvold, Pierson, Horral, George, Pegg, 1957 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Yellowstone County; Donald J. Luebbe, C.A., 1958 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Yellowstone County; Don Luebbe, Robert Bucher, Agents; Alfreda Forswall, D. D. A; Joe Horrall, H. Maxwell, Merle Lyda, Assoc. Agents; Don Pegg, At Large, 1959 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Yellowstone County; Robert Bucher, Alfreda Forswall, Merle Lyda, Ruth Pierson, Harold Strobel, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Yellowstone County; R. F. Bucher, John Ranney, Robert Racicot, Alfreda Forswall, Ruth Pierson, Merle Lyda, 1961 (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Yellowstone County; Robert F. Bucher, Alfreda Forswall, John E. Ranney, Ruth K. Pierson, Robert G. Racicot, 1962 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Yellowstone County; Robert Bucher, John Ranney, Robert Racicot, Alfreda Forswall, Ruth Pierson, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Yellowstone County; George Goodwin, Alfreda Forswall, Robert Bucher, Ruth K. Pierson, John Ranney, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Yellowstone County; Robert Bucher, Alfreda Forswall, John Ranney, Ruth Pierson, 1965 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Yellowstone County; John Ranney, Thomas Herrin, Alfreda Forswall, Ruth Pierson, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Yellowstone County, 1967-1970 (Box 70, Folder 3-6)
- Indian Reservation Agents Annual Reports, 1955-1970; 2
  In the early years of the Extension Service, agents posted in counties adjacent to Montana's Indian reservations assumed some of the duties associated with working for the various tribes on an ad hoc basis, but beginning in 1955 agents were specifically assigned to the task. Six of Montana's reservations had an assigned agent, all initially supervised by Verne Dusenberry. As in the case of the county agents, Indian reservation extension agents filed annual reports on their activities. The folders in this series have been arranged alphabetically by reservation name, and then chronologically within that reservation name sort.
  - Blackfeet Reservation; John O. Toliver, Robert E. Durham, Bonita J. Olney, 1955 (Box 70, Folder 7)